{
    "subject": "resource/Boxing_Legends_of_the_Ring",
    "predicate": "ontology/developer",
    "object": "resource/Sculptured_Software",
    "human_readable": "The developer of Boxing Legends of the Ring is Sculptured Software.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.846710741519928,
            "question": "Has Sculptured Software won any awards for Boxing Legends of the Ring?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6864174008369446,
            "question": "What platforms is Boxing Legends of the Ring available on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6842272281646729,
            "question": "What is the name of the company that created Boxing Legends of the Ring?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5875319838523865,
            "question": "What are some popular features of Boxing Legends of the Ring?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5794464349746704,
            "question": "Who developed the video game Boxing Legends of the Ring?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5491965413093567,
            "question": "Is Sculptured Software known for developing other types of games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41692137718200684,
            "question": "Are there any sequels or spin-offs of Boxing Legends of the Ring?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37643682956695557,
            "question": "When was Boxing Legends of the Ring released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35491907596588135,
            "question": "What makes Boxing Legends of the Ring unique compared to other boxing games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.261924147605896,
            "question": "What type of video game is Boxing Legends of the Ring?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The developer of Boxing Legends of the Ring is Sculptured Software.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6649_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Boxing Legends of the Ring unique compared to other boxing games?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6649_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Boxing Legends of the Ring released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6649_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any sequels or spin-offs of Boxing Legends of the Ring?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6649_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6649_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6649_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6649_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6649_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6649_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6649_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6649_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6649_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6649_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6649_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents explicitly state that \"Boxing Legends of the Ring is a boxing game, developed by Sculptured Software and published by Electro Brain,\" which confirms that Sculptured Software is indeed the developer of Boxing Legends of the Ring."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}